<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Canary - Home page</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Canary - Home page</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromxt.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Textbooks for Linear Algebra</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/textbook_linear_algebra/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/textbook_linear_algebra/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Linear Algebra is not what it seems at first thought. Behind all the matrices, polynomials, vectors and spaces, there is a fascinating subject which tools can help you to solve many practical problems. I want to recommend some intuitively clear linear algebra textbooks for self-taught.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>How to solve slow boot on Ubuntu</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/how_to-solve_boot_slow_ubuntu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/how_to-solve_boot_slow_ubuntu/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I just installed Ubuntu on my old laptop, and everything seems to work well, except booting the system. It could take several minutes to an hour or more to login desktop. After logging in, there&amp;rsquo;s a black screen and my cursor, nothing else! I found out that &lt;code&gt;drm_kms_helper-errors&lt;/code&gt; occur repeatedly and takes a lot of time each. What does this mean and how do I fix it? If it can&amp;rsquo;t be fixed, how do I prevent it from using so much time when booting?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Some piece of curated articles about https explain</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/https_explain/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/https_explain/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;For newbies, its difficult to understand all the technical jargon words which just bounce above your head. However its not a rocket science, we would see what https does and how its going to benefit or help us on web.What is https? https is “Hyper Text Transfer Protocol Secure”, the safe way to browse site or page which is encrypted and secure to send or receive private data or information.What is SSL?
How it Works? How to Identify Secure Connection?&amp;hellip;.I&amp;rsquo;ll share some good pieces to explain it simplely.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Peg Solitaire Game</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/peg_solitaire/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/peg_solitaire/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peg_solitaire&#34;&gt;Peg Solitaire&lt;/a&gt; is a game in which you need to remove every piece of pegs from the board except one. To remove a ball, you must jump over it with another one. A valid move is to jump a peg over an adjacent peg into a hole two positions away and then to remove the jumped peg. Only vertical or horizontal movement is allowed in most board types. Diagonal movement is allowed only in the Triagular board. This may sound easy, but without a good strategy, you will get stuck sooner or later.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>QR Code Generator</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/qr_code_generator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:35:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/qr_code_generator/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I just use &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/neocotic/qrious&#34;&gt;qrious.js&lt;/a&gt; to implement a simple QR code generator.Please feel free to try online QR code generator to make your own QR codes. It supports four levels of error correction, you can choose the right size for your QR codes in the range of 100 to 1000 and click on a color swatch in the swatches panel to change the foreground and backgroud color.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Deploying a Hugo Blog with GitHub Actions</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/deploying_a_hugo_blog_with_github_actions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/deploying_a_hugo_blog_with_github_actions/</guid><description>We already can use Travis-CI and Netlify to build and deploy Static Sites, Today we introduce a new way to automate and customize your workflows&amp;ndash;GitHub Actions. But we’re just scratching the surface of what GitHub Actions can do. Once you get started, you’ll be able to build, package, release, update, and deploy your project in any language—on GitHub or any external system—without having to run code yourself.
Sign up for the limited public beta of GitHub Actions</description></item><item><title>Top textbooks for data structures</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/top_textbooks_for_data_structures/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 21:20:01 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/top_textbooks_for_data_structures/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The algorithms reading roadmap is: Algorithms -&amp;gt; CLRS -&amp;gt; Introduction to Analysis of Algorithms -&amp;gt; TAoCP.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Never Binge Again, by Glenn Livingston</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/never_binge_again/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 22:00:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/never_binge_again/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Doubt and low self-esteem are the psychological cancers which fuel overeating behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pig is not you.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>How to enable DNS-over-HTTPS (DoH)</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/how_to_enable_doh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 07:35:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/how_to_enable_doh/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog-cloudflare-com-assets.storage.googleapis.com/2019/10/DoT-DoH@2x.png&#34; alt=&#34;05_01.png&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Math for Computer Science and Machine Learning</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/math_for_cs_ml/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 12:23:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/math_for_cs_ml/</guid><description>Prof. Gallier, who&amp;rsquo;s a Professor in the Computer and Information Science Department, School of Engineering and Applied Science at the University of Pennsylvania, launches a new book Algebra, Topology, Differential Calculus, and Optimization Theory For Computer Science and Machine Learning.That&amp;rsquo;s almost 2,000 pages of math,“math basics” is quite the misnomer—it gives the impression that one would need to study all of the contents of this book to be an effective practitioner in CS or ML.</description></item><item><title>Intermittent Fasting Is Good For You</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/intermittent_fasting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 07:07:22 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/intermittent_fasting/</guid><description>Intermittent fasting (IF) is currently one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular health and fitness trends. People are using it to lose weight, improve their health and simplify their lifestyles.Many studies show that it can have powerful effects on your body and brain and may even help you live longer.
Researchers have discovered that meal timing strategies such as intermittent fasting or eating earlier in the daytime appear to help people lose weight by lowering appetite rather than burning more calories, according to a report.</description></item><item><title>Algorithms by Jeff Erickson</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/algorithms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 18:23:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/algorithms/</guid><description>Algorithms by Jeff Erickson
🔥1st edition, June 2019 🔥
(Amazon links: US, UK, DE, ES, FR, IT, JP)
This web page contains a free electronic version of my self-published textbook Algorithms, along with other lecture notes I have written for various theoretical computer science classes at the University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaign since 1998.
More information Get the book More algorithms lecture notes Models of computation notes Report an error (separate page) Coursework archive (separate page) More Information Publication.</description></item><item><title>How to roll your own X</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/how_to_roll_your_own_x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 08:23:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/how_to_roll_your_own_x/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;One of your strengths at work lately has been quickly getting up-to-speed on technologies, techniques, tools, or skills that you&amp;rsquo;ve never encountered before.self-development is by itself already an attractive quality as it shows interest in your work/field and that&amp;rsquo;s especially true when you can use what you&amp;rsquo;ve learned to improve your work&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Remote PwdHash</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/pwdhash/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 14:01:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/pwdhash/</guid><description>Site Address
Site Password
Hashed Password
Version 0.8 (more versions)
PwdHash generates theft-resistant passwords.The PwdHash browser extension invisibly generates these passwords when it is installed in your browser.You can activate this protection by pressing F2 before you type your password, or by choosing passwords that start with @@.If you don&amp;rsquo;t want to install PwdHash on your computer, you can generate the passwords right here.</description></item><item><title>You and Your Research</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/your_and_your_research/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 13:34:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/your_and_your_research/</guid><description>Richard Hamming Transcription of the Bell Communications Research Colloquium Seminar 7 March 1986 J. F. Kaiser Bell Communications Research 445 South Street Morristown, NJ 07962-1910 jfk@bellcore.com
At a seminar in the Bell Communications Research Colloquia Series, Dr. Richard W. Hamming, a Professor at the Naval Postgraduate School in Monterey, California and a retired Bell Labs scientist, gave a very interesting and stimulating talk, &amp;lsquo;You and Your Research&amp;rsquo; to an overflow audience of some 200 Bellcore staff members and visitors at the Morris Research and Engineering Center on March 7, 1986.</description></item><item><title>Introduction to HTTP/3</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/intro_to_http3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 08:23:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/intro_to_http3/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;HTTP is the application protocol that powers the Web. It began life as the so-called HTTP/0.9 protocol in 1991, and by 1999 had evolved to HTTP/1.1, which was standardised within the IETF (Internet Engineering Task Force). HTTP/1.1 was good enough for a long time but the ever changing needs of the Web called for a better suited protocol, and HTTP/2 emerged in 2015. More recently it was announced that the IETF is intending to deliver a new version - HTTP/3. To some people this is a surprise and has caused a bit of confusion. If you don&amp;rsquo;t track IETF work closely it might seem that HTTP/3 has come out of the blue. However, we can trace its origins through a lineage of experiments and evolution of Web protocols; specifically the QUIC transport protocol.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Happy New Year Everyone!💖</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/hapy_new_year_2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/hapy_new_year_2019/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://f000.backblazeb2.com/file/canicula/ImgURL/happy-2019-year.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;avatar&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>IPSec Modes: Transport and Tunnel</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/ipsec_modes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/ipsec_modes/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;IPSec modes are closely related to the function of the two core protocols, the Authentication Header (AH) and Encapsulating Security Payload (ESP). Both of these protocols provide protection by adding to a datagram a header (and possibly other fields) containing security information. The choice of mode does not affect the method by which each generates its header, but rather, changes what specific parts of the IP datagram are protected and how the headers are arranged to accomplish this. In essence, the mode really describes, not prescribes how AH or ESP do their thing. It is used as the basis for defining other constructs, such as security associations (SAs).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s take a look at how the two modes work.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Collection of some useful websites</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/some_useful_webs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 21:03:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/some_useful_webs/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Here are the most useful websites on the Internet that will make you smarter, increase productivity and help you learn new skills. These incredibly useful websites solve at least one problem really well.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title> EnglishPod 1-365 transcripts</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/englishpod/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 11:44:10 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/englishpod/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://f000.backblazeb2.com/file/canicula/ImgURL/elp.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dsd.jpg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EnglishPod pod ast is very good english material.This pod ast has losed down since EnglishPod moved to OpenLanguage in 2013.
This page lists all transcripts of the 365 episodes dialogs:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Install Mercury&#39;s MW150UH/300UH WiFi USB Adapter driver on Unbunt 18.04</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/install_mercury_driver_ubuntu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:41:59 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/install_mercury_driver_ubuntu/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The MW150UH/MW300UH 11N Wireless USB Adapters auto-sensing capability allows high packet transfer rateof up to 150Mbps/300Mbps for maximum throughput. It has good capability on anti-jamming; it can alsointeroperate with other wireless products. The adapter supports WEP, WPA and WPA2 encryptionto prevent outside intrusion and protect your personal information from being exposed. But we can only download the Window verison drives for them from official website. But How to make enable the wifi adapters on Ubuntu 18.04.You can follow the steps below.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chrome 69 no longer displaying www in domain names</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/chrome69_subdomain_missing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 13:23:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/chrome69_subdomain_missing/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;As we know, Chrome 69(9.0.3497.81)has reached the stable branch and is now available for us on September 4, 2018, When you update to the lastest version, you will find that Chrome 69: “www.” subdomain is missing from URL,.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google suddenly cuts characters from address bar for the sake of brevity (yeah right), confusing the heck out of us.The truncation is the result of Chrome programmers considering www to be a &amp;ldquo;trivial&amp;rdquo; subdomain, and setting it to be removed from the address bar.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Free Sites to Receive SMS Online</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/free_sms_receive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/free_sms_receive/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Many web services nowadays require a phone verification system. They send a verification code to your cell phone number that you have to enter on the website. If you do not feel comfortable of receiving a SMS every time you sign up for an online service, there are numerous websites that could help you to receive that specific SMS on a Computer.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Awesome Go</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/awesome-_go/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/awesome-_go/</guid><description>Awesome Go
A curated list of awesome Go frameworks, libraries and software. Inspired by awesome-python.
Contributing Please take a quick gander at the contribution guidelines first. Thanks to all contributors; you rock!
If you see a package or project here that is no longer maintained or is not a good fit, please submit a pull request to improve this file. Thank you! Contents Awesome Go</description></item><item><title>Awesome Networking</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/awesome-_networking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/awesome-_networking/</guid><description>Awesome Networking A curated list of awesome networking libraries, resources and shiny things.
HTTP
HTTP: The Definitive Guide HTTP/1.1 HTTP/2 draft High Performance Browser Networking TCP/IP
TCP/IP Illustrated tcpdump Beej&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Network Programming The C10K problem Tornado Linux source code TCP Hybla DNS
DNS Protocols and APIs
SOCKS Protocol Version 5 tuntap NAT Android VpnService Network Extension Cryptography
Cryptography Block cipher mode of operation libsodium - A modern and easy-to-use crypto library.</description></item><item><title>The Algorithms of Python</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/algorithms_python/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/algorithms_python/</guid><description>The Algorithms - Python All algorithms implemented in Python (for education) These are for demonstration purposes only. There are many implementations of sorts in the Python standard library that are much better for performance reasons.
Sort Algorithms Bubble From Wikipedia: Bubble sort, sometimes referred to as sinking sort, is a simple sorting algorithm that repeatedly steps through the list to be sorted, compares each pair of adjacent items and swaps them if they are in the wrong order.</description></item><item><title>What are some of the best lightweight websites?</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/text-only-websites/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/text-only-websites/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Read the news without using up all of your bandwidth. A wide variety of sites offer text-only versions that work on any computer , but they’re occasionally buried and hard to find on the modern web.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are more than a few reasons to want to know where these sites are, however. Maybe you don’t like clutter? Maybe you’re one of the millions still using dial-up, and want a low-bandwidth way to read news? Maybe you regularly tether your computer to your smartphone, but don’t have an unlimited data plan? Maybe you like to read the news on your e-reader and want clean sites for doing so? Or maybe you want a list of quick-to-load news sources in case a disaster slows down your Internet connection just when you need it most.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whatever your reason, find a list of links to mobile news sites that work on any computer below, without the need for tricks like user agent switchers.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>