<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Miscellaneous on Canary - Home page</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/categories/miscellaneous/</link><description>Recent content in Miscellaneous on Canary - Home page</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:35:20 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromxt.github.io/categories/miscellaneous/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>QR Code Generator</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/qr_code_generator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:35:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/qr_code_generator/</guid><description>I just use qrious.js to implement a simple QR code generator.Please feel free to try online QR code generator to make your own QR codes. It supports four levels of error correction, you can choose the right size for your QR codes in the range of 100 to 1000 and click on a color swatch in the swatches panel to change the foreground and backgroud color. main section { min-width: 250px; max-width: 50%; height: 100%; text-align: center; } main img { box-shadow: 0 0 10px 5px #666; } main form { padding: 25px 0 50px 0; text-align: left; } main textarea { display: flex; justify-content: center; align-items: center; } main form label { display: block; margin-top: 10px; color: #444; font-weight: bold; } main form input, main form select { margin: 0 auto; width: 100%; } main form input:invalid { outline: 2px solid #f00; color: #f00; } 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30 31 &amp;lt;form autocomplete=&amp;#34;off&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;label&amp;gt; value &amp;lt;textarea type=&amp;#34;text&amp;#34; name=&amp;#34;value&amp;#34; spellcheck=&amp;#34;false&amp;#34; class=&amp;#34;form-control&amp;#34; style=&amp;#34;width:100%; height:150px;&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Input your url&amp;lt;/textarea&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/label&amp;gt; &amp;lt;label&amp;gt; size &amp;lt;input type=&amp;#34;number&amp;#34; name=&amp;#34;size&amp;#34; placeholder=&amp;#34;100&amp;#34; min=&amp;#34;100&amp;#34; max=&amp;#34;1000&amp;#34; value=&amp;#34;250&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/label&amp;gt; &amp;lt;label&amp;gt; level &amp;lt;select name=&amp;#34;level&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;option value=&amp;#34;L&amp;#34;&amp;gt;L - 7% damage&amp;lt;/option&amp;gt; &amp;lt;option value=&amp;#34;M&amp;#34;&amp;gt;M - 15% damage&amp;lt;/option&amp;gt; &amp;lt;option value=&amp;#34;Q&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Q - 25% damage&amp;lt;/option&amp;gt; &amp;lt;option value=&amp;#34;H&amp;#34;&amp;gt;H - 30% damage&amp;lt;/option&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/select&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/label&amp;gt; &amp;lt;label&amp;gt; background &amp;lt;input type=&amp;#34;color&amp;#34; name=&amp;#34;background&amp;#34; value=&amp;#34;#ffffff&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/label&amp;gt; &amp;lt;label&amp;gt; foreground &amp;lt;input type=&amp;#34;color&amp;#34; name=&amp;#34;foreground&amp;#34; value=&amp;#34;#000000&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/label&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/form&amp;gt;</description></item><item><title>Deploying a Hugo Blog with GitHub Actions</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/deploying_a_hugo_blog_with_github_actions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/deploying_a_hugo_blog_with_github_actions/</guid><description>We already can use Travis-CI and Netlify to build and deploy Static Sites, Today we introduce a new way to automate and customize your workflows&amp;ndash;GitHub Actions. But we’re just scratching the surface of what GitHub Actions can do. Once you get started, you’ll be able to build, package, release, update, and deploy your project in any language—on GitHub or any external system—without having to run code yourself.
Sign up for the limited public beta of GitHub Actions</description></item><item><title>Never Binge Again, by Glenn Livingston</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/never_binge_again/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 22:00:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/never_binge_again/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Doubt and low self-esteem are the psychological cancers which fuel overeating behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pig is not you.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Intermittent Fasting Is Good For You</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/intermittent_fasting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 07:07:22 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/intermittent_fasting/</guid><description>Intermittent fasting (IF) is currently one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular health and fitness trends. People are using it to lose weight, improve their health and simplify their lifestyles.Many studies show that it can have powerful effects on your body and brain and may even help you live longer.
Researchers have discovered that meal timing strategies such as intermittent fasting or eating earlier in the daytime appear to help people lose weight by lowering appetite rather than burning more calories, according to a report.</description></item><item><title>How to roll your own X</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/how_to_roll_your_own_x/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 08:23:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/how_to_roll_your_own_x/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;One of your strengths at work lately has been quickly getting up-to-speed on technologies, techniques, tools, or skills that you&amp;rsquo;ve never encountered before.self-development is by itself already an attractive quality as it shows interest in your work/field and that&amp;rsquo;s especially true when you can use what you&amp;rsquo;ve learned to improve your work&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Remote PwdHash</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/pwdhash/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 14:01:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/pwdhash/</guid><description>Site Address
Site Password
Hashed Password
Version 0.8 (more versions)
PwdHash generates theft-resistant passwords.The PwdHash browser extension invisibly generates these passwords when it is installed in your browser.You can activate this protection by pressing F2 before you type your password, or by choosing passwords that start with @@.If you don&amp;rsquo;t want to install PwdHash on your computer, you can generate the passwords right here.</description></item><item><title>You and Your Research</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/your_and_your_research/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 13:34:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/your_and_your_research/</guid><description>Richard Hamming Transcription of the Bell Communications Research Colloquium Seminar 7 March 1986 J. F. Kaiser Bell Communications Research 445 South Street Morristown, NJ 07962-1910 jfk@bellcore.com
At a seminar in the Bell Communications Research Colloquia Series, Dr. Richard W. Hamming, a Professor at the Naval Postgraduate School in Monterey, California and a retired Bell Labs scientist, gave a very interesting and stimulating talk, &amp;lsquo;You and Your Research&amp;rsquo; to an overflow audience of some 200 Bellcore staff members and visitors at the Morris Research and Engineering Center on March 7, 1986.</description></item><item><title>Collection of some useful websites</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/some_useful_webs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 21:03:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/some_useful_webs/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Here are the most useful websites on the Internet that will make you smarter, increase productivity and help you learn new skills. These incredibly useful websites solve at least one problem really well.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title> EnglishPod 1-365 transcripts</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/englishpod/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 11:44:10 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/englishpod/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://f000.backblazeb2.com/file/canicula/ImgURL/elp.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dsd.jpg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EnglishPod pod ast is very good english material.This pod ast has losed down since EnglishPod moved to OpenLanguage in 2013.
This page lists all transcripts of the 365 episodes dialogs:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chrome 69 no longer displaying www in domain names</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/chrome69_subdomain_missing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 13:23:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/chrome69_subdomain_missing/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;As we know, Chrome 69(9.0.3497.81)has reached the stable branch and is now available for us on September 4, 2018, When you update to the lastest version, you will find that Chrome 69: “www.” subdomain is missing from URL,.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google suddenly cuts characters from address bar for the sake of brevity (yeah right), confusing the heck out of us.The truncation is the result of Chrome programmers considering www to be a &amp;ldquo;trivial&amp;rdquo; subdomain, and setting it to be removed from the address bar.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Free Sites to Receive SMS Online</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/free_sms_receive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/free_sms_receive/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Many web services nowadays require a phone verification system. They send a verification code to your cell phone number that you have to enter on the website. If you do not feel comfortable of receiving a SMS every time you sign up for an online service, there are numerous websites that could help you to receive that specific SMS on a Computer.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>What are some of the best lightweight websites?</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/text-only-websites/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/text-only-websites/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Read the news without using up all of your bandwidth. A wide variety of sites offer text-only versions that work on any computer , but they’re occasionally buried and hard to find on the modern web.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are more than a few reasons to want to know where these sites are, however. Maybe you don’t like clutter? Maybe you’re one of the millions still using dial-up, and want a low-bandwidth way to read news? Maybe you regularly tether your computer to your smartphone, but don’t have an unlimited data plan? Maybe you like to read the news on your e-reader and want clean sites for doing so? Or maybe you want a list of quick-to-load news sources in case a disaster slows down your Internet connection just when you need it most.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whatever your reason, find a list of links to mobile news sites that work on any computer below, without the need for tricks like user agent switchers.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>