<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>computer on Canary - Home page</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/categories/computer/</link><description>Recent content in computer on Canary - Home page</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromxt.github.io/categories/computer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Textbooks for Linear Algebra</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/textbook_linear_algebra/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/textbook_linear_algebra/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Linear Algebra is not what it seems at first thought. Behind all the matrices, polynomials, vectors and spaces, there is a fascinating subject which tools can help you to solve many practical problems. I want to recommend some intuitively clear linear algebra textbooks for self-taught.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>How to solve slow boot on Ubuntu</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/how_to-solve_boot_slow_ubuntu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/how_to-solve_boot_slow_ubuntu/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I just installed Ubuntu on my old laptop, and everything seems to work well, except booting the system. It could take several minutes to an hour or more to login desktop. After logging in, there&amp;rsquo;s a black screen and my cursor, nothing else! I found out that &lt;code&gt;drm_kms_helper-errors&lt;/code&gt; occur repeatedly and takes a lot of time each. What does this mean and how do I fix it? If it can&amp;rsquo;t be fixed, how do I prevent it from using so much time when booting?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Some piece of curated articles about https explain</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/https_explain/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/https_explain/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;For newbies, its difficult to understand all the technical jargon words which just bounce above your head. However its not a rocket science, we would see what https does and how its going to benefit or help us on web.What is https? https is “Hyper Text Transfer Protocol Secure”, the safe way to browse site or page which is encrypted and secure to send or receive private data or information.What is SSL?
How it Works? How to Identify Secure Connection?&amp;hellip;.I&amp;rsquo;ll share some good pieces to explain it simplely.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Top textbooks for data structures</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/top_textbooks_for_data_structures/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 21:20:01 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/top_textbooks_for_data_structures/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The algorithms reading roadmap is: Algorithms -&amp;gt; CLRS -&amp;gt; Introduction to Analysis of Algorithms -&amp;gt; TAoCP.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>How to enable DNS-over-HTTPS (DoH)</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/how_to_enable_doh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 07:35:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/how_to_enable_doh/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog-cloudflare-com-assets.storage.googleapis.com/2019/10/DoT-DoH@2x.png&#34; alt=&#34;05_01.png&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Math for Computer Science and Machine Learning</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/math_for_cs_ml/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 12:23:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/math_for_cs_ml/</guid><description>Prof. Gallier, who&amp;rsquo;s a Professor in the Computer and Information Science Department, School of Engineering and Applied Science at the University of Pennsylvania, launches a new book Algebra, Topology, Differential Calculus, and Optimization Theory For Computer Science and Machine Learning.That&amp;rsquo;s almost 2,000 pages of math,“math basics” is quite the misnomer—it gives the impression that one would need to study all of the contents of this book to be an effective practitioner in CS or ML.</description></item><item><title>Algorithms by Jeff Erickson</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/algorithms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 18:23:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/algorithms/</guid><description>Algorithms by Jeff Erickson
🔥1st edition, June 2019 🔥
(Amazon links: US, UK, DE, ES, FR, IT, JP)
This web page contains a free electronic version of my self-published textbook Algorithms, along with other lecture notes I have written for various theoretical computer science classes at the University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaign since 1998.
More information Get the book More algorithms lecture notes Models of computation notes Report an error (separate page) Coursework archive (separate page) More Information Publication.</description></item><item><title>Introduction to HTTP/3</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/intro_to_http3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 08:23:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/intro_to_http3/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;HTTP is the application protocol that powers the Web. It began life as the so-called HTTP/0.9 protocol in 1991, and by 1999 had evolved to HTTP/1.1, which was standardised within the IETF (Internet Engineering Task Force). HTTP/1.1 was good enough for a long time but the ever changing needs of the Web called for a better suited protocol, and HTTP/2 emerged in 2015. More recently it was announced that the IETF is intending to deliver a new version - HTTP/3. To some people this is a surprise and has caused a bit of confusion. If you don&amp;rsquo;t track IETF work closely it might seem that HTTP/3 has come out of the blue. However, we can trace its origins through a lineage of experiments and evolution of Web protocols; specifically the QUIC transport protocol.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>IPSec Modes: Transport and Tunnel</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/ipsec_modes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/ipsec_modes/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;IPSec modes are closely related to the function of the two core protocols, the Authentication Header (AH) and Encapsulating Security Payload (ESP). Both of these protocols provide protection by adding to a datagram a header (and possibly other fields) containing security information. The choice of mode does not affect the method by which each generates its header, but rather, changes what specific parts of the IP datagram are protected and how the headers are arranged to accomplish this. In essence, the mode really describes, not prescribes how AH or ESP do their thing. It is used as the basis for defining other constructs, such as security associations (SAs).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s take a look at how the two modes work.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Install Mercury&#39;s MW150UH/300UH WiFi USB Adapter driver on Unbunt 18.04</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/install_mercury_driver_ubuntu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:41:59 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/install_mercury_driver_ubuntu/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The MW150UH/MW300UH 11N Wireless USB Adapters auto-sensing capability allows high packet transfer rateof up to 150Mbps/300Mbps for maximum throughput. It has good capability on anti-jamming; it can alsointeroperate with other wireless products. The adapter supports WEP, WPA and WPA2 encryptionto prevent outside intrusion and protect your personal information from being exposed. But we can only download the Window verison drives for them from official website. But How to make enable the wifi adapters on Ubuntu 18.04.You can follow the steps below.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>RESTful API Basic</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/restful_api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/restful_api/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;REST (RESTful) API — stands for representational state transfer and runs mostly on the programming language JSON. Most public APIs use this because of its fast performance, dependability and ability to scale by reusing modular components without affecting the system as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>