<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Miscellaneous on Canary - Home page</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/tags/miscellaneous/</link><description>Recent content in Miscellaneous on Canary - Home page</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromxt.github.io/tags/miscellaneous/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploying a Hugo Blog with GitHub Actions</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/deploying_a_hugo_blog_with_github_actions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/deploying_a_hugo_blog_with_github_actions/</guid><description>We already can use Travis-CI and Netlify to build and deploy Static Sites, Today we introduce a new way to automate and customize your workflows&amp;ndash;GitHub Actions. But we’re just scratching the surface of what GitHub Actions can do. Once you get started, you’ll be able to build, package, release, update, and deploy your project in any language—on GitHub or any external system—without having to run code yourself.
Sign up for the limited public beta of GitHub Actions</description></item><item><title>Never Binge Again, by Glenn Livingston</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/never_binge_again/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 22:00:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/never_binge_again/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Doubt and low self-esteem are the psychological cancers which fuel overeating behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pig is not you.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Remote PwdHash</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/pwdhash/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 14:01:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/pwdhash/</guid><description>Site Address
Site Password
Hashed Password
Version 0.8 (more versions)
PwdHash generates theft-resistant passwords.The PwdHash browser extension invisibly generates these passwords when it is installed in your browser.You can activate this protection by pressing F2 before you type your password, or by choosing passwords that start with @@.If you don&amp;rsquo;t want to install PwdHash on your computer, you can generate the passwords right here.</description></item><item><title>Collection of some useful websites</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/some_useful_webs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 21:03:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/some_useful_webs/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Here are the most useful websites on the Internet that will make you smarter, increase productivity and help you learn new skills. These incredibly useful websites solve at least one problem really well.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>What are some of the best lightweight websites?</title><link>https://fromxt.github.io/post/text-only-websites/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromxt.github.io/post/text-only-websites/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Read the news without using up all of your bandwidth. A wide variety of sites offer text-only versions that work on any computer , but they’re occasionally buried and hard to find on the modern web.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are more than a few reasons to want to know where these sites are, however. Maybe you don’t like clutter? Maybe you’re one of the millions still using dial-up, and want a low-bandwidth way to read news? Maybe you regularly tether your computer to your smartphone, but don’t have an unlimited data plan? Maybe you like to read the news on your e-reader and want clean sites for doing so? Or maybe you want a list of quick-to-load news sources in case a disaster slows down your Internet connection just when you need it most.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whatever your reason, find a list of links to mobile news sites that work on any computer below, without the need for tricks like user agent switchers.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>